http://www.auspen.org.au/privacy-policy

Members AREA
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy applies to all personal information collected byAuSPEN via the website located at www.auspen.org.au.How to contact us about privacyYour privacy is very important to us. For that reason, please read thefollowing details carefully and get in contact with us if you have anyquestions. You can contact us on: admin@auspen.org.auCollection and PurposeWe may collect personal information from you in the course of your websiteif you input any personal information into the website. In addition, wealso collect cookies from your computer, which enables us to tell when youuse the website and also to help customise your website experience.The purpose for which we collect personal information is to provide youwith the best service experience possible on the website. Some provisionof personal information is optional. However, if you do not provide uswith certain types of personal information, you may be unable to enjoy thefull functionality of the website.DisclosureWe customarily disclose personal information only to our service providerswho assist us in operating the website. We will only disclose personalinformation to an unrelated third party with your consent.National Privacy Principle 6 of the Australian Privacy Act 1998 (Cth)allows you to get access to, and correct, the personal information we holdabout you in certain circumstances. If you would like to obtain suchaccess, please contact us on the details set out above.Access and correctionWe have processes in place to ensure the security of your personalinformation, including encryption of all data when it is transferred toour service providers and limitations on access to personal informationwithin our organisation.Security
